cheetahmail.com 2018-12-26

# Cheetah Digital Website Privacy Policy

© Copyright 2018- Cheetah Digital

Contact usCareersBlog

Cheetah Digital (“Cheetah”, “We”, “Us”, and “Our”) provides global marketing technology and services which enable our Customers to centrally manage marketing data, orchestrate electronic communications and gain actionable insights into their customer engagement across multiple channels.

This Policy applies solely to the information we collect and use on our corporate websites, including  **www.cheetahdigital.com**  and  ****

**www.dedicatedtomarketers.com,** or other Cheetah websites that link to this Privacy Policy (collectively referred to as the “Website”). This Policy does not apply to our email and cross-channel campaign management platforms (collectively, “Services”). 

  * This Privacy Policy explains how Cheetah Digital collects, uses, shares and secures the personal data you provide on our Websites, as well as your choices regarding use, access and correction of your personal data

  * For information on our privacy practices as they related to our marketing platforms, please see our  **Services Privacy Policy**

  * To learn how Cheetah Digital meets the requirements of the European Union’s General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”), please visit our  **GDPR Guide**

  * To learn more about our firm commitment to not providing software or services used for sending unsolicited commercial electronic messages ('spam'), please refer to the  **Global Anti-Spam Policy.**

  * For visitors to our Websites and recipients of our Customers’ electronic communications, please refer to our  **Tracking Technology** ** ** and  **Message Recipient**  privacy guides.

##  Quick Reference

  * _I_ _nformation We Collect and Use_ __
  * _Grounds for Using Your Personal Data_ __ __
  * _Information Sharing and Legal Notice_ __
  * _Website Activity_ __
  * _Client and Business Inquiry Communications_ __
  * _Cookies and Similar Technologies_ __
  * _Social Media Features and Widgets_ __
  * _Online and Targeted Advertising_ __
  * _Website Security and Retention_ __
  * _Access and Your Privacy Rights_ __
  * _International Data Transfers_
  * _Links_ __
  * _Notification of Changes to This Policy_
  * _Contact Us_

##  Information We Collect and Use

We are the exclusive owner of information collected about you through our websites. We collect personal data you may volunteer to us while using the Website such as name, company, email address, and phone number. We may also collect personal data through our blog,  **Dedicated to Marketers** , when you post a comment and when you interact with us through social media widgets (described below under “Social Media Features and Widgets”). You should be aware that any information you provide in these public areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal data from our blog or community forum, contact us at  **[privacy@cheetahdigital.com](mailto:privacy@cheetahdigital.com?subject=Privacy%3A)**. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal data, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

We collect this information and use it for internal business purposes and web operations and to engage with our Customers, prospective Customers and visitors to our websites. Before we use or otherwise process your personal data for any other reason, we will provide you information on that further processing and any other additional relevant information. As a permission-based marketing services provider, we detest 'spam'.

  * If you visit our website and volunteer your email address, we will send you appropriate information at your request, such as a white paper. Additionally,

  * If you are our corporate Customer or are interested in becoming one, we may use the email address you volunteer to send you important information regarding our products and services, as well as promotions that we deem relevant.

  * If information requested is directed to a third-party-related interest, we may share the information with an appropriate third-party in order to fulfill the directed request.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services, contact us at  **[privacy@cheetahdigital.com](mailto:privacy@cheetahdigital.com?subject=Privacy%3A)**. We will retain and use your information for our legitimate business interests to deliver our services, comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our contracts.

##  Grounds for Using Your Personal Data

When administering the website Cheetah Digital acts a data controller relying on the following lawful grounds to collect and process your personal data:

  * Legitimate business interests. We may use your personal data for our legitimate business interests to improve our websites and content, and to optimize your experience. Consistent with our legitimate business interests and any choices that we offer or consents that may be required under applicable laws and regulations, we may use personal data and technical information for direct marketing.

  * Performance of contract. We need to collect and use your personal data to enter into a contract with you or to perform a contract that you have with us. For example, when you express interest in our services we will use the business contact information you provide to respond to your requests and provide you with such Services.

  * User Consent. We may use personal data described in this Privacy Policy subject to your consent. Notably and where required by applicable laws and regulations, we will rely on your consent for electronic marketing and personalization of message content, which may include collecting information from your mobile device or computer. You may withdraw your consent at any time using thing opt-out and preference management mechanisms provided within the message or by contacting us as described in this Privacy Policy. Withdrawing consent will not affect the lawfulness of consent-based processing before consent was withdrawn. 

##  Information Sharing and Legal Notice

We may share your information with third parties who provide services on our behalf to help with our business activities. These companies are authorized to use your personal data only as necessary to provide these services to us. These services may include fulfilling orders or purchases, payment processing, validating contact information, sending marketing communications, and providing cloud infrastructure.

From time to time we may also share your information with third party business partners, for instance, for the purpose of enhancing our products and services, or so that they may market their events, venues, products or services to you. If you do not want us to share your personal data with these companies, contact us at  **[privacy@cheetahdigital.com](mailto:privacy@cheetahdigital.com?subject=Privacy%3A)**.

In certain situations, Cheetah Digital may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements. We may also disclose your personal data as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena or other legal process, when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or properly respond to a government request.

If we are involved in a merger, acquisition, dissolution or sale of all or a portion of its assets, we reserve the right to transfer your personal data. You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our website of any change in ownership or uses of your personal data, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal data.

##  Website Activity

We track visitors to our corporate website, as well as provide our platform Customers with services enabling additional website activity reporting. In addition to cookie and pixel tag uses we describe below, website visitor tracking also involves the automatic collection of web server log file data, including Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, web pages visited, operating system, date/time stamp, clickstream data, unique visitations, type of browser used, and other session-based activity. Web server log file information, by itself, is not linked to any personally identifiable information and is used to analyze trends in the aggregate and administer the site.

Cheetah Digital is not responsible for website activity monitoring on Customer websites, by Customers or any other third parties.

##  Client and Business Inquiry Communications

We reserve the right to moderate the content of respondent postings and publish the name and website of our  **Dedicated to Marketers**  blog respondents in association with their comments. We take no responsibility for the accuracy or other content with our respondent postings. If you believe a respondent comment is inappropriate or deserves further analysis by a corporate representative, please  **contact us**.

In addition, we may occasionally send Customers or previous business inquiries, including blog respondents, email messages with product updates, educational events, or other important business related information. Each email includes an opportunity to unsubscribe from future messaging, or recipients can contact us directly through any of our  **points of contact**  or at  **[privacy@cheetahdigital.com](mailto:privacy@cheetahdigital.com?subject=Privacy%3A)**.

##  Cookies and Similar Technologies

We, our service providers, and/or non-affiliated third parties, may use "cookies" or similar technologies such as "pixel tags" on our digital properties. As described below, we and our partners use cookies or similar technologies in order to analyze trends, administer the websites, track users' movements around our digital properties, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. You can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level, but if you choose to disable cookies, it may limit your use of certain features or functions on our website or service.

We use these technologies with our website visitors in a de-identified fashion. We may also use third party analytics and marketing integration services such as those by Google, Salesforce and BrightFunnel to help us track and optimize our website performance and corporate marketing. 

These third parties may also use both cookies and pixels to help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. These third parties are prohibited from using collected data for any purpose other than as a service provider to us. For more information on these partners’ privacy practices, you can refer to their specific privacy policies listed below:

  * **https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout**

  * **https://www.salesforce.com/company/privacy/**

  * **http://www.brightfunnel.com/privacy-policy/**

Please note that these terms do not refer to cookies enabled through Customer-access portals to our marketing platforms, nor Customer-specific applications through other domain names we may host on their behalf. For inquiries regarding Customer software access or Customer-specific uses of cookies, please contact your Customer services representative.

For more information about how we use cookies and similar technologies, please refer to our 

 **Tracking Technology Guide** **.**

##  Social Media Features and Widgets

We use Social Media Features, including the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Share button or similar interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These features may collect your IP address and other personal data including which page you are visiting on our site and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social Media features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. Refer to the below section covering online targeting to learn how you can limit such collection. For more information on the technologies used by these social networks, please refer to their specific privacy policies listed below:

  * Facebook:  **http://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/**

  * Google+:  **https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/**

  * LinkedIn: ** https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy**

  * Twitter:  **https://twitter.com/privacy**

If you provide us your personal data, we may use it to interact with you on these social networks. Our interactions with you would also be subject to that network's privacy policy, terms of use, and your consent as appropriate. 

##  Online and Targeted Advertising

While we do not do so at this time, we reserve the right to use cookies or similar technologies to serve online advertising on our websites and to identify unique customers or prior blog respondents. We may work with advertising partners to deliver targeted advertising related to Cheetah Digital's own products and services. To facilitate targeted advertising, we and our third-party partners may utilize "cookies" or equivalent identifiers (explained above) and other audience matching technologies. We use data elements from our corporate marketing databases to assist us in presenting appropriate offers to our prospective Customers.

We may also work with advertising networks, advertising exchanges, and/or other types of advertising technology providers such as Google to enable the delivery of relevant online targeted advertising to our corporate Customers' customers while respecting consumer privacy and offering choices about participating in such activities.

In addition, third parties may collect data about browsing activities on our websites and other unrelated websites over time, for online targeted advertising purposes.

Our advertising partners may place a pixel tag or cookie on certain websites, such as a website registration page. This enables our partner companies to later display a relevant advertisement to you based on your website browsing behavior. This type of online, targeted advertising — known as "retargeting" — is used to re-engage consumers who previously visited a website. To measure the effectiveness of the online targeted advertising you see, we partner with companies to evaluate your interactions with the ads. Certain information may be collected and shared with these partners, including what ad you received, when you viewed it and whether you clicked on the ad.

You can opt-out of online targeted advertising from companies participating in the Digital Advertising Alliance program through the  **DAA Consumer Choice page** , which is available in versions for desktop and mobile browsers. The DAA also offers a separate choice tool for the collection of cross-app data on mobile devices for online targeted advertising and other applicable uses. To exercise choice applicable to companies participating in this choice tool, you can install the DAA's  **AppChoices app**. European residents may opt-out of targeted advertising using the  **IAB Europe opt-out platform.**

Please ensure you review the opt-out choices available to you within the applicable policies on other Cheetah Digital owned, affiliated, or operated websites.

##  Website Security and Retention

Safeguarding the personal data you give us or we receive about you is important to us. Your information is maintained in a secure environment, and our team of security professionals continually monitors our web interface touch-points to detect and thwart any attempts at unwanted intrusion. Cheetah Digital takes appropriate security measures to protect against loss, misuse and unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure, or destruction of your information.

We take commercially reasonable steps to ensure the ongoing confidentiality, integrity, availability and resilience of our systems and services processing your personal data.

We will retain your personal information for the length of time needed to fulfil the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law.

##  Access and Your Privacy Rights

If you are our Customer or prospect, you may access, correct or request deletion of your personal data. If your business contact information changes, or if you would like to modify or remove your details, or to exercise your other rights, please contact your Customer Services representative or contact us using the information described below. 

Cheetah Digital respects and acknowledges that individuals frequently desire to access their personal information, or make other requests regarding their personal rights. However, we have no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data we process on behalf of our Customers. An individual consumer who seeks access to personal data concerning them, or who seeks to correct, amend, request processing restrictions, object to processing, or delete personal data or exercise a right of portability should direct his or her query to the respective Cheetah Digital Customers. If requested by a Customer to provide assistance with such requests, we will respond within 30 days.

If you have any questions about our collection and use of your personal data, please contact us at 

 **[privacy@cheetahdigital.com](mailto:privacy@cheetahdigital.com)**.

##  International Data Transfers

We maintain facilities and offices around the world, including in the United States, the UK, France, Germany, Australia and Japan. Your personal data may be transferred to, stored, or processed outside of your country or the country in which you were located when you initially volunteered the information. 

As a global marketing technology and services provider working on behalf of our international Customers, we take many steps to protect the personal data in our care, including offering contractual assurances to this effect. Should the relationship with one of our group companies, Customers or partners involve cross-border data flows outside the European Union, we shall formally undertake to comply with the best data protection standards by adhering to the  **Standard Contractual Clauses adopted by the European Commission.**

##  Links

Our web content and corporate communications may contain links to other sites. Cheetah Digital is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of these sites. We recommend users read the privacy statements of each linked website.

##  Notification of Changes to This Policy

If we decide to change our website and tracking privacy practices, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this Policy at any time. If we make material changes to these statements, we will notify you on this page prior to the changes taking effect.

##  Contact Us

Please direct any questions or comments regarding our privacy policy or practices to us at:

Cheetah Digital  
Attention: Privacy  
222 Broadway, 17th Fl  
New York, NY 10038  
Email:  **[privacy@cheetahdigital.com](mailto:privacy@cheetahdigital.com)**

Or contact us using this online  **form**

If you wish to escalate your inquiry after contacting the privacy team, you are welcome to contact our Data Protection Officer, ePrivacy GmbH, at  **[dpo@cheetahdigital.com](mailto:dpo@cheetahdigital.com).**

ePrivacy GmbH  
Represented by: Prof. Dr. Christoph Bauer

Große Bleichen 21  
20354 Hamburg  
Sitz Hamburg  
HRB118163

Complaints   
You have the right to complain to a Data Protection Authority about our or our Customers’ collection and use of your personal data. For more information, please contact your local authority (contact details for data protection authorities in the European territories are available  **here** ).
